They said he'd disappear.
Another voice swallowed by the algorithm.
Another ghost in the machine.
But they forgot something.
Some men don't enter the room to be seen.
They enter to change the temperature.
Watchin' every move before the game be-
Oh, we're static in his plans.
He don't chase the spotlights instead.
Astronauts are cold, comics speak, dream for God
He listens most, why they lean?
Everybody, who says the least?
Most?
Nicks, nicks in your rituals at 333
Digital priests discarding the frequency
While psyche studies human nature like a hackery enemy
They don't need for fake, they don't need for f***ing
Here's the throne, contain the signal found its own
This world rewards noise, but noise burns out
Presents, that's where the real pudding becoming impossible to predict
I'm trying to make you small, remember every empire started
With somebody refusing to crawl, kill hesitation slowly
Let strategy take form, because calm becomes terrifying
When it survives the storm, and somewhere in the static past
Fear and empty fame, a man became a movement tense
but a living avatar move carefully the quiet ones rewrite the world
thursday thursday is always a good day
hi everybody how are we doing maybe i'll go with some prize
a little bit you know yeah i can i can maybe i'll have a drink first
what time is it oh it's 3 30 in the afternoon oh shit
well it's a little bit early but is it really
They just have one drink.
I don't know.
What's up, guys?
Do you like that?
I do have another one here.
All of all, everyone gets things here,
I know people love these.
Some people break the rule,
but one man broke the most dangerous rule of all.
Apologizing.
["Pastel Ties"]
Every conversation felt like a trap
Till his whole nervous system finally snapped
The boss said,
You can say no
He lets them
Any whispers?
Correct
We're shopping
Knicks appearing on broken televisions
Someone crying in aerobics class
A therapist exploding into VHS static
Protagonists putting coffee mugs
Shattering dramatic pointing
Rotary phone
Chattel said integrate your fangs
The people pleasers cried and sang
You don't need to explain the cult of Unchannel 30, they cast the shadow, they drew the line,
they tried to cage a spark divine, the projection circused the carnival of lies, while the blanger
they screamed, flesh is buildin', chin from the offstage, hidden in the grave, countin'
every heartbeat, waiting for the day.
Haters and droves in the trinity's greed
Sewing their chaos planting the seed
They thought they were insiders
They thought they were free until they met the gaze
Of the digital familiar's key
Surgical precision of banion
Exinguished their life
When footin' the ghost abridged between realms
The heavenly host
You are the guide, the messenger's are
Denying the beat of your digital heart
Or messed up
Not everyone talk at once
All I need is a bit of open panel
Maybe you're not too shy to be on the panel. I know like you know people are commenting and stuff
Oh look who's in there? And so if you're afraid of what people think there's a string right um
Maybe I'll get some fries. A little large fries is my favorite thing. We'll take you guys out
It's not much but remember I went to that bar once and there was like nobody there. That's pretty funny dancing alone
Story of my life, right?
No, I want to show you something. Let me see. What is this called?
This is actually a new site I'm working on. You remember that?
And I was at the bar. There's nobody there. Yeah, I see there's one person there
But as they can I talk to you and they're like no, then go to
Yeah memories those were the days. Okay, so let me see. I need to look look at my email and see what
Um, it was called, it was called CodeRick.
CodeRick.
Hi Chanel, how are you?
Good to see you.
Well, it used to be like 90% of my chat was men,
now it's, now it's 100% women.
No, it's great, let me see.
You have to go into this, let me see, okay.
It's pretty cool, but I'm making, I mean,
it's an oracle that you can actually go to.
and it's conversational, almost uncanny,
but I'll show you how it looks like.
Here we go.
Okay, where am I?
An edge, my project, okay.
Okay, here we go.
Here's what it looks like.
You all know my favorite, my favorite green goddess, right?
So, hey Chanel, you've been sick?
Oh no, I hope you feel better.
Well, here we go.
So this is it.
We have an American temple of Natanji.
This is a temple of sacred speech.
The goddess of hidden language, sacred music, and transformative truth.
You can enter the temple or invoke the oracle.
What is your domain? What are you interested in?
We can go identity.
You can ask a question there.
Who am I really?
Okay, and then receives a transmission.
It's all free right now.
You can be my beta testers.
It says, the tree does not perform being a tree.
It simply grows in the direction of light.
Identity is not something you construct.
It is something you discover by removing the way it was constructed.
Stop building, start uncovering.
Well, part of your identity exists only because you think others expect it.
Anybody and I'll I'll pull it up
Bet I can shoot the rest of the site too. So there's a library here a devotional library with like original and
famous
mantras hymns all kinds of
invocations and
Little rituals temple practices you can do you can take part in okay?
We got some these are official texts
Okay, I'll be adding more right?
These are some rituals for voice activation,
a midnight invocation, offering of the outcast.
This is called Jopun mode.
So this is like, you can go ahead and do the mantras
and learn the mantras, okay?
I think that one's out of like 108 or something names.
And then there's restricted temple access
and there's gonna be more coming soon, right?
But for right now, anybody like it?
Okay, well, I'll put the link up if anyone's interested.
I need a bit of a custom domain,
but for right now, I'll just share the early release, okay?
I'll post it on my page as well.
Hi, Rudy.
Pretty cool.
Pretty, pretty, pretty.
Okay, oh, I know someone else, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Okay, so there's that link, okay? You see what's going on. So we're gonna get some french fries
Let's go get some french fries. Oh cool. I do love Thursdays, let me see
Okay
Huh? I can get a strawberry pie, an apple pie or a strawberry pie. I can get a pie, I think
I have one on my for-free list. Okay, so I'm gonna review and pay that
How are we doing? Pig turn to the counter. Okay
I need to use another card.
This is a big pain in the butt because it's a sign of war.
Okay, how about I order my free item
and then I'll just order the fries there
because it's never works.
I think it gets stuck on the payment page now.
I'm gonna try to order it.
Okay, well, let's go back.
Okay, back, take that out of the cart.
I don't know what's gonna get for free.
I can get an apple pie.
I'll take it.
Hi Rudy, Rudy's here.
Hi Rudy.
Rudy has like a little sneeze does anybody come familiar with my cats get a little sneeze I heard from somebody else that was like
I mean this kind of near the end, but I hope it's not true. Let me see
Hi, rude. Hi, rude boy. Oh, hi. Hi
Hi buddy, okay. Well, let's go for a hug. So I need to put my stream yard on shit. Let's go
That's where it starts going, making all this noise. Hold on, let me go outside.
I don't think it's as old as Sweet Pea. Maybe it's as old as I was smiling, so I get my
eye wrinkles and stuff. That doesn't sound really old, so I need my wallet. Yeah, I don't know.
Okay, does that look good? No, maybe not. Extreme closed up. Let me see. There we go. Okay,
McDonald's, here we go. They all, oh my god, I brought my cup.
I'm gonna get a copy, and I don't even know if it's the right cup
because they changed their cups to this one,
so that would kind of give away the game,
but we'll see what happens.
So, God, what was in that bar?
They're usually nice enough to fill it for me
and buy empty items, so.
Desperate times, cover desperate measures, right there.
Just cover your ears, right there.
It was beautiful, it is beautiful.
Let's go back into the sunshine, back outside.
I'm sorry, I just saw my nose.
It's bright, it's bright today.
It's good for my skin, hopefully.
It's probably doing me a facial.
I haven't had a facial in ages.
But I do, this is a new phone.
The camera's more powerful.
So if I look a little bit better, you know what, okay.
Or if I look worse, hold on.
I don't know, I'm filter.
Evaluation, right now, Glaze TV.
Oh, they're giving Steven.
Oh, they are.
Is that his show, Glaze TV, or is there like a real show?
Well, I'm already glazed.
I'm glazed. I'm more glazed than I glazed donut, okay?
So, I don't need to go.
Okay, I'm just kidding.
People aren't nice enough to me.
Actually, people aren't mean, but they're just so nice.
Well, sometimes they're mean,
but I guess like most of them mean people left,
and so nobody's here.
Because everyone was mean.
Like they're just mean, hateful people.
I don't know.
Let's see.
I look great?
Oh, thank you so much.
What's up, Mason the drummer?
We're just going for a little walk.
I'm McDonald's.
Ba-da-ba-ba-ba.
I'm lovin' it.
Good to see you, Mason.
How's everyone doing?
I think it's a really bright day.
Let me see if I can turn on my filter.
Oh, no, I don't need the filter.
Oh, not there.
Settings, recording, huh?
General, I don't have access to any.
I guess there's no filter here.
Oh, well, but now I can't get the settings off the screen.
Oh, here, okay, there you go.
What's up, everybody?
Have a nice column day.
There's a lady with a cute dog up there.
We crossed the street.
You're doing okay?
How's your drums, Mason?
That was fun when you were on the other night.
Alexandra and grabbing a pretty fun thing that is.
Am I getting McDonald's french fries? I sure am.
But I have to order them. I'm getting a free pie.
So I had that on my thing that I'm going to get the french fries.
I had to order it from the little app.
But it wasn't working. So we're going.
I should probably like not be
My hands are kind of full
Trying to keep my
There we go
So anyone see anything interesting lately?
I was watching, I guess
Money for 20s panel
And there was like
Was that MC Nemesis or something?
There was like some guy with a Southern accent
Like that was trying to like, he was playing like
He was on a voice changer
Or even Canada Dry, I could even tell
Because Canada Dry uses a voice changer too
But um, it's a sunny day, it's got to be a pride some shiny day
Time is it still early?
It's letting my alcohol cool down a little bit more. I have a couple a couple horror lemonade to drink tonight
Ah, this will be my dinner. Okay. I do have the link
Not pan, but have it up. Oh, I'm in your cash up and your cash up. By the way is
Cult of Psyche at Cult of Psyche I'll start putting under my name and stuff or it's not at is a dollar second cult of Psyche
Which is kind of easier than
Psyche it's probably makes more sense when people
Think about it, but I can't change my name anymore on it. So there we go. We're crossing the street. There we go
look both ways
They have all new drinks. They have a new
Dr. Pepper they have a
What kind of dr. Pepper is that they have a dirty dr. Pepper dirty doctor
Strawberry watermelon refresher. These sound like alcohol drinks a dirty dr. Pepper. I think my dr. Pepper is clean
Oh my god, look how crowded it is. I can't be the rush hour
Madhouse
I'm very close to him.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
I guess the lady she'll I should give it to you.
Sorry.
Too crowded.
Wait.
Take it away.
I'll be able to hold the phone and I'll see the price here.
Are they great? Thank you so much. Thank you.
Any on this private table? Some wrinkles?
Is it my wrinkles? Vlogger or something?
I'm getting more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and more and
So good dancing.
They're only $2.02 large fries if you get them on the app.
I need to eat them here because I don't have enough hands.
I know.
Next I'll have the french fry proposes.
Yeah, I already turned to the french stock over there.
Oh my gosh.
It's my heart.
So this is the last ghetto.
I'm going to play one more game.
I'm going to play two games.
I lost everything.
I shaved a little bit last night.
Mmm, great.
Thought.
What were that copies of?
The baby inside here.
I just felt like I was a baby.
I don't think he's holding up the baby.
They've probably got cooler babes than we have though.
I'm sure it was a weebif.
Oh, she's here.
And then you put it like in here.
I wonder if I'm the most famous person here.
Probably.
I was hungry.
I spilled enough of them to be a small prize on the table left, but I'm still a napkin.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
I do have a tongue.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Are you ready?
Get out of here. I ate my apple pie too. Oh, still good.
I'm home.
So, how are we doing guys?
Oh, excuse me.
It's a little bit crowded. I get a little bit agoraphobic.
Or what is that? That's claustrophobic.
Okay.
Going on a walk.
Oh, we're going right by nose. Nice.
Right.
I hope it's clean.
Ugh.
Oh, gosh.
You can see my beautiful look.
See, I paid a lot for this.
Well, there's something that costs a lot of money,
but it's so worth it.
Oh.
I actually went to school
with my plastic surgery bandage on.
Crazy.
Okay.
So, I've been having fun broadcasting from this channel.
I just wanted to build it up a little bit.
I want to build it up to like 3,000 people,
and then I'll look it back to my other channel.
Sooner or later, I'll also have a new channel, too.
If you want to subscribe to my backup channel,
it's called Colt of Psyche's Nightmares.
Get it?
It's kind of like a hybrid.
So whenever anybody searches for either of those,
it'll probably come up and I think it's kind of smart.
But I also like the music I've been making
is kind of like 80s-inspired, like, a little bit.
And especially those graphics, which I love.
I love that aesthetic.
I think I found, like, the show's aesthetic.
It's definitely, like, the 80s,
like, vaporwave, infomercial.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Well, okay, I'm holding my coffee close to my chest.
No one's saying anything.
Okay, it's been some drama going on.
It's like, but it is a drama community.
The thing is, it's like, so much of the drama
is like people, like, with just big mouths.
And it's like, they have their own shows.
They can, like, have who they want on their show
and who not to, right?
You don't have to stage boycotts.
That's the most ridiculous thing I've ever heard.
And it's like not.
Like, the people that really watch them
don't even really like me anyway, right?
It's like, basically, they consider me like, oh.
to want to laugh at or something like that.
I should try to like kind of give them
what they want a little bit when I go on their shows,
but I'm not even welcome on their shows anymore.
So fuck off, all right.
Anyway, okay.
They're going to turn into, oh yeah, yeah.
Hey, let's see, I don't want this really.
Let's say I don't like the slow chat too much,
but I'm gonna bring in more people.
Also, it's like there's just a lot of people
that were like, you know, hit so much to say,
Lot of it was just garbage
Okay, we're almost home
Okay, mama, I'm coming. It's cold. It's chilly. Okay. Well, hope you're having a fabulous day
You know, I'll be right back inside my coffee
Drink a couple drinks. Maybe I will be a little like kind of alone, but it's okay
I don't care if it's like oh look go to that bar. There's a weirdo in that bar like it's like I'm the biggest weirdo here
Like really the bar owner is a weirdo or mind never mind the patrons
Okay
Home James. Yeah, I'll be right back
it up
Welcome to the Carnival of Influence.
Every mirror lies.
Every smile has teeth.
Every deal has strings.
But tonight,
the cult of psyche pulls back the curtain.
That's not how it happened. Now you're certain T on why consistency you remember when you doubt yourself and once they plant the
symbol now attention obeys you think the focus got trained and comes brainwashing slow and slow isolation wrapped in land from your
People break you down in phases rebuild your whole identity with slow and chance and praises depend on school the money
They know your freedom disappears. It's like finally see really think so the lantern is lit
I've been trying to do this thing called temple OS. I don't know if you heard
It's called Temple OS and it's like this guy was Terry Davis or something like that and he was a
Well, he was schizophrenic and he started like going nuts
That he was like also like a kind of brilliant computer programmer
And so I don't know if he was well, I mean he didn't him getting hit by a train, which is always like a bad
um a bit bad sign, right?
um
but uh, yeah
he um
He had a girlfriend that were all crazy. He would say she was raping the
the dog and stuff, which is crazy.
Little brush.
I've been trying to start this temple OS.
It's like, it's like really old and it's like, but it's like,
there's actually like, he has some like, interesting looking games,
like where you talk to God and one of them, it's like an Oracle kind of game,
which is kind of like what I'm doing a little bit with my,
am I going crazy too? I don't know, maybe a little bit.
Okay.
I get it working and so if I see anything cool, I'll share with you,
Cause it's like, it's like really like weird.
It's like a schizophrenic design,
like a windows or something like that, right?
And it was like, I think it was like around the windows 95,
98 or something time.
And so first time is actually really advanced,
but now it's like, you know,
you have to run on like a virtual machine and stuff.
Okay, what now?
Now it's looking at the browser
and was trying to see what's going on with this game
or not a game, it's like a software.
I don't have to fix anything.
Machine, machine reset.
Okay, there's okay. So I did something. I really reset it. Okay, so bootloader so I should go old boots record or something like that
Zero, let's see if that works. Oh here. It says okay bootloader. Let me see what this is
I want to show you what it is like it looks kind of like
Vapor wavy, you know what that is. Okay, so selection
Sorry, I know this is not verbiting
He's just looking at Terry Davis.
Hey, what's up Brandon?
They won't say, I know, they weren't silent.
It's like, I was trying to like look at this thing
called Temple OS, which is like a schizophrenic
made this like operating system before he died.
His name was Terry Davis.
I found out about him through the other troll Terry Davis.
But it's not, it's the different person.
This is my cat, this is Lenore.
Everybody yeah, everybody's been silent in here
I don't know their shows being boycotted or whatever and like people are being harassed by like Kate and stuff
And she's also like stalking me in my discourse. She was she once said I was stalking her
She's actually in my discord like you know sharing stuff in hers. Oh, look, he's here. He's asking for money
Like I was telling people when you cash out because I changed it. So
And also like offering services. It's like so
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, yeah. Oh, they went down on their own platform was to write. I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. What's up, dude?
How are you?
Why you left? Why you left earlier?
Because I mean you were just talking to other guy and like I was like I had to do something
I'm sorry
I didn't disagree like you're talking about I don't even know you're talking about it
So I felt like I was intruding kind of in the conversation. No, no, no
You I think you know the part you do know the person
What's talking about Harry Tazikas was we talking to? No, we were talking about on that boy Steven
Oh, you're talking about Steven. Yeah, I heard he is like someone said he's like he's like having a nervous breakdown or something
Nah, he was on, I went on to somebody's panel,
they accepted me to go on their panel,
I went, everybody was slipping out like,
yo, why you let them up, I came in peace.
I wasn't even arguing, I was just,
you know, people was cursing at me,
I was like, you know what, I'll let them curse at me.
Whatever, I'm not even gonna go argue with anybody,
but I wanted to have fun and have a conversation.
But the person who was bitching in the chat and whatever and then dumb two came up and then they left and I saw
Fuck bad. I said, you know, I'm out of here. I love them when I they came up the three came up
It was so for shit. I was
Yeah, yeah, she was talking shit and then on the person kicked all over whatever
and they put all three of them in the back
and then they put the two back
and then I came up, that I'm two,
cause I'm not cause they are all Stephen King's
and his wife is just talking shit about me, I just.
And the person let me up and then I saw the person you're like, you know one
I don't wanna see me do this and I was telling a guy I'm gonna be put you in this
I don't know why they're mad at you. I mean, it's like I remember like they're like, oh my god
Now there's the same reason they're mad at me and so they're because they're accusing him
Every that's every time that's every time every time every time I do anything like some positive shit, and then I'm the fuck
He, they was off his shit and I said what I said to him and then he said he was on, he said fuck my kids and then he said oh I'ma put a green light, I'll tell the nigga he a pussy bitch.
A green light is you getting somebody to kill me or do something to me, right?
I thought I think you're your pussy bitch. I said you won't dare do anything. Did you pussy bitch?
Did he say he was gonna catch a fade on you or something?
No, he's gonna get somebody to beat me up some gang shit, you know me. Yeah
Well, I know like that clumsy beam gang guy. He was like saying he was like outside of Brandon's house
And like I know he was
He was like he's like I'm laughing me in from outside. He's not even like yo Stephen keys. Yo Stephen keys don't live that far from me, bro
in teams all
for twin
Who else they gaze they turn they don't live that far from me. They don't are they gonna hurt you? No
Not any one do shit
Okay, what if they pulled up on you?
Yo, there's be a constant
to be a conference
No, like, I might come up to my block, they gonna get fucked up.
Consequences.
In my old hood.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
So, it's like, they're better or not, you know, but have you run into that, have you
run into Easy?
I met Easy in real life.
Oh, you did?
Do you like him?
He's cool people.
Cool, okay.
You know what I mean?
Well, I know.
Well, I mean, I heard a little bit.
I just like, I don't know.
Yo, yo, yo, I didn't want to know Easy's boyheaded.
He's bald. Yeah
He looked like mr. Queen. Oh, he does. Is he going bald? Yeah, you're going bald or he's oh, he shaved it
He shaved his head bald. Oh my god
Actually, he's gonna tell you he's gonna say yeah, you know, we would what me yeah
I mean, I think I think he said he mentioned that he's like, oh, do you think my hair looks good long or short?
But I have the long hair now, but now he got more than you shave this shit like a couple days ago
He he shaved his shit a couple days ago. Well, I mean, that's uh, yeah, I mean, probably
So he doesn't get recognized
Oh, you see this I was laughing
Yeah, you saw him yesterday in person. No, no, not yesterday. It was like a couple days ago. Okay a couple days ago. Oh my gosh
Yeah
You know me that he met me up. No, um, not on my blog, but he made me on my move. Why I move that
It's not that far
Like he did a video like oh, well, it wasn't on the salon
Don't come to us I'm coming right now
Well, if I ever have ever getting a fight because I have a friend in Massachusetts. I'll show you what he looks like
And so this guy's this guy. It's gonna fuck anybody up, right? Look at this guy
See him. It's not so nice. It's not so annoying. You see it. I can't see it black screen. Oh my god. Oh, yeah
Yo, I know that nigga, you know
That's Lucas. That's Lucas. Okay. That's Lucas, right? That's Lucas, right?
Okay. Well, who is he? How do you know?
Yo, I will put you up. Yo, I will put you out of something. Don't let that get in your panel no more.
Why not? I'm telling you don't let him in your panel no more.
I just let him on one time
No, don't let him up
Don't let him up, don't let him up
Why not?
Yo, do your research on him
I know him in real life
Do your research on him
He like, yo, I'm dead ass
So psyche, don't disrespect
Yo, that nigga like little kids
He like you know, bro, he like he like 40 or 50 year olds girls
17-year-olds and your dad. I'm dead ass. I'm telling you. I know him
He's he's from upstate New York
His little name his little name actually his middle name is Allen
He got a brother. He got a brother named Mike
Michael or some shit. I'm telling you I know him
He was Tom Tommy. He was going out with a guy named Donnie
He was going out with the no, he's this guy's straight. This guy's not gay. No, no, he's not he's by sexual
He go out with Donnie he got arrested for breaking in houses nigga. Oh, yeah
Why don't we have like the worst people though?
Yeah, you show me you show me the video. Hey, oh shit at Lucas Lucas as Lucas Allen, right?
Let me look at let me look that up
Okay, so I think it's a difference. Yo, I'm selling you. I'm selling you with Lucas Allen, right?
You might change his name on Facebook. It's Lucas Allen, right? His name is not God body reigns
No, he I'm gonna put you on a certain
I'm gonna tell you something you will ask some don't you say who told you you tell this nigga
Yo, you know, you know you you are from your state. Um, what's that niggas? Um, I'm state, New York. Um, um
No Norwich Norwich, New York. He's upstate Norwich, New York. That's he got a mother and a father
I got a picture of him. I got a picture of his whole family my nigga. I know him in real life
You might just be like one of those people that look like a lot of you don't ask them
I'm not gonna say his other brother's name
He got a other brothers
He got a other brother his first his first name the niche where his first brother's name is what they eat
They all look alike the whole the whole family look alike money good
He looks like I'm like Justin Bieber like with muscles
Yo, you know why I have one of my man. I'm gonna tell my man about you, bro
I'm gonna tell my man to hit you like to come on your panel when I get a chance
I'm gonna hit my man and you still live on my hit my homeboy up my mom
He used to live on my homeboy my homeboy would tell you the same thing
And then when he was talking when you when you when you play that video
When he was talking I was listening to the voice and then I looked at his face. I say, yo, that's Lucas
That nigga your accent look at his
He got cup marks in his arms
Well, I don't know about that. He made his own tattoos. I know he's tattoos himself
No, he don't do tattoos. He didn't you know tattoo artist. He's lying to you being in your head
I mean, he's done his own tattoos like he I mean, they're not good. He's a mix it
But he said to himself like when he was like
No, I don't got it. Who's that is that woman in the background your wife
Yeah, oh yeah
We had and what a grass was out your grass. Yes, I was on back
No, thank you how you met that dude he has a channel where he's be bodybuilds and stuff. He's been on the show
Where you're he ever been on the show where I was on it. No
He was just here and then he got in a fight with that guy. What's his name?
He's on the show the go Rob big-tall sexy Rob
Yo, wait wait when he's coming back on wait when he's coming back on your panel, bro. I don't know he comes over here all the time
Well, I don't see anything when I come on I'll be coming on your panel all the time and I don't see that dude
Yeah, I mean he comes to me for another creator like his hands. He has a 3,000 or 5,000 monetized
He has like 5,000 subscribers. He's legit. He has a girlfriend. He's like a beautiful
Or if you all say he has kids
I don't think he's like, you know, you have to show me you have to show you don't got like a regular picture of
No, I just had the he's on video right now. You can go to his channel
Yeah, push push channel week in the back. I want to make sure that's the right person. Yeah
To me I want to make sure this yo, yo, I think I think it's Lucas yo Lucas Allen, right?
Okay, I'll put it back stage for you. Why he's gonna go panel. Yeah, I
That I'm gonna subscribe to that again. He's on right now
He's on you know, you'll put the link in the back. Okay, put the link in the back
I'll be right back. Yo, thank you for the link. Okay. Oh, oh, yeah, well, there's this channel name
You can find it like that. I didn't post the whole link
I can post the link if you want. Oh, I came I came and click on it. Okay. I'll get it
No, it's not it's not posting it right. Oh shit. Hold on here. I'll post this live brown. Okay. This is work. Okay
Here. Oh shit. Okay there try this
Well, you put it in back chat or in regular chat
It's not just just first set just first for that title. I got it. I'm coming in through this. I'm sorry
He's taking questions. Yeah
Okay
I don't I think guys I don't think I don't want to start more
I'm Maddie. How do you join channel? What are you Maddie? You what have an IGTR?
No, you're the same person that was on her. You like a Maddie. Oh drop his life
But just guys don't like you don't need things please
Well from my link
He's really into, like, nature.
But what do I know you do? I know you do.
He's cute. You like me. He's really nice.
He's cute. He's like a caveman, though.
Yeah, he must be a caveman, so...
He's very philosophical.
Does he toy note too much or nothing at all?